let questions = [
    {
        id: 01,
        question: 'Who won the 10th Italian Open title in 2021?',
        alternatives: ['Novack Djokovic', 'Rafael Nadal', 'Dominic Thiem', 'Stefanos Tsitsipas'],
        correct: 'Rafael Nadal',
        expo: 'The winner of the 2021 Italian Open <br> was Rafael Nadal. He secured his 10th title at <br> the tournament by defeating Novak Djokovic in the final.',
    },

    {
        id: 02,
        question: 'India won Thomas Cup on May 15, 2022, by defeating whom?',
        alternatives: ['Indonesia','Malaysia', 'China', 'Denmark'],
        correct: 'Indonesia',
        expo: 'India took on 14-time winners <br> Indonesia in the final of the Thomas <br> Cup in Bangkok on May 15, 2022.',
    },

    {
        id: 03,
        question: 'Only three countries have won the Womens Rugby World Cup - New Zealand, England, and who?',
        alternatives: ['USA','Argentina','Romania','Georgia'],
        correct: 'USA',
        expo: 'USA was on of the three contries that won the Womens Rugby World Cup along with New Zealand and England',
    },

    {
        id: 04,
        question: 'In cricket which of the following fielding positions is behind the batsman?',
        alternatives: ['Mid-wicket','First slip','Cover','Mid-off'],
        correct: 'First slip',
        expo: 'In cricket first slip fielding position is behind the batsman',
    },

    {
        id: 05,
        question: ' Who is the first Indian fencer to qualify for the Tokyo Olympic Games?',
        alternatives: ['Kavitha Devi','Bhavani Devi','Daina Devi','Kaushik Vedika'],
        correct: 'Bhavani Devi',
        expo: 'Tamil Nadus Bhavani Devi the 1st Indian fencer <br> to qualify for the Olympics, was felicitated by <br> Indian Fencing Association.',
    },

    {
        id: 06,
        question: 'The term ‘Dolphin Kick’ is associated with which of the following games?',
        alternatives: ['Badminton','Squash','Swimming','Golf'],
        correct: 'Swimming',
        expo: 'The Dolphin kick technique is used by professional swimmers, <br> they use that motion that propels them forward underwater <br> after diving in, and at the underwater turns.',
    },

    {
        id: 07,
        question: 'Chelsea’s new manager is Graham Potter. Potter represented 11 different English clubs during his playing career. Where did he start his management career?',
        alternatives: ['Norway','Sweden','Denmark','Finland'],
        correct: 'Sweden',
        expo: 'Graham Potter started his management in Sweden',
    },

    {
        id: 08,
        question: 'Neeraj Chopra won Indias first-ever Olympic Gold Medal in which of the following sports?',
        alternatives: ['400m Hurdle','Javelin Throw','Long Jump ','High Jump'],
        correct: 'Javelin Throw',
        expo: 'Neeraj Chopra is an Indian track <br> and field athlete, who is the reigning Olympic <br> champion and World champion in Mens Javelin throw.',
    },

    {
        id: 09,
        question: 'Novak Djokovic began the Wimbledon fortnight as the world No. 3 player. What is his current position in the world rankings?',
        alternatives: ['No 1','No 3','No 7','No 9'],
        correct: 'No 7',
        expo: 'His current position in the world rankings is No 7',
    },

    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Who became the first player of Indian origin to play in an NBA game?',
        alternatives: ['Sim Bhullar','Palpreet Singh','Amjyot Singh','Satnam Singh'],
        correct: 'Sim Bhullar',
        expo: 'Sim Bhullar became the first player of Indian origin to play in an NBA game?',
    },

]